[
  {
    "question": "1 + 1 = ",
    "A1": 1,
    "A2": 2,
    "A3": 3,
    "A4": 5,
    "Answer": "A2"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 2 = ",
    "A1": 1,
    "A2": 2,
    "A3": 3,
    "A4": 5,
    "Answer": "A3"
  },
  {
    "question": "1 + 4 = ",
    "A1": 1,
    "A2": 2,
    "A3": 3,
    "A4": 5,
    "Answer": "A4"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 1 = ",
    "A1": 3,
    "A2": 5,
    "A3": 7,
    "A4": 11,
    "Answer": "A1"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 3 = ",
    "A1": 3,
    "A2": 5,
    "A3": 7,
    "A4": 11,
    "Answer": "A2"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 5 = ",
    "A1": 3,
    "A2": 5,
    "A3": 7,
    "A4": 11,
    "Answer": "A3"
  },
  {
    "question": "2 + 9 = ",
    "A1": 3,
    "A2": 5,
    "A3": 7,
    "A4": 11,
    "Answer": "A4"
  },
  {
    "question": "3 + 5 = ",
    "A1": 8,
    "A2": 13,
    "A3": 124,
    "A4": 16,
    "Answer": "A1"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 + 5 = ",
    "A1": 8,
    "A2": 13,
    "A3": 124,
    "A4": 16,
    "Answer": "A2"
  },
  {
    "question": "8 + 8 = ",
    "A1": 8,
    "A2": 13,
    "A3": 124,
    "A4": 16,
    "Answer": "A4"
  }
]
